Guide to the McKinney Family Papers, 1823-1964
Archives and Special Collections Library, Vassar College Libraries
- SERIES III. John Luke McKinney, 1863-1959
  - Letter to Ethelyn from J. L. McKinney [Titusville, PA], 6 Apr 1917 (Folder 5.22)
  - Letter to Ethelyn from J. L. McKinney, 7 Apr 1917 (Folder 5.23)
  - Letter to Ethelyn from J. L. McKinney, 14 Apr 1917 (Folder 5.24)
  - Letter to Ethelyn from J. L. McKinney, 16 Apr 1917 (Folder 5.25)
  - Letter to Ethelyn from J. L. McKinney, 22 Apr 1917 (Folder 5.26)
  - Letter to Ethelyn from J. L. McKinney, 29 Apr 1917 (Folder 5.27)
  - Letter to (Ethelyn?) from J. L. McKinney [Titusville, PA], 30 Apr 1917 (Folder 5.28)
  - Letter to Ethelyn from J. L. McKinney, 12 May 1917 (Folder 5.29)
  - Letter to Ethelyn from J. L. McKinney [New York], 19 June 1917 (Folder 5.30)
  - Letter to Ethelyn from J. L. McKinney, 1 July 1917 (Folder 5.31)
  - Letter to family from J. L. McKinney, 4 July 1917 (Folder 5.32)
  - Letter to Ethelyn from J. L. McKinney [Clove Valley, La Grangeville, NY], 23 Aug 1917 (Folder 5.33)
  - Letter to Ethelyn from J. L. McKinney, 25 Nov 1917 (Folder 5.34)
  - Letter to Ethelyn from J. L. McKinney, 26 Nov 1917 (Folder 5.35)
  - Letter to family from J. L. McKinney, 27 Nov 1917 (Folder 5.36)
  - Clippings: "Standard Dividends" and "Step Lively Last Night's Attraction", undated; (2) (Folder 5.37)
  - Letter to family from J. L. McKinney, 23 Mar 1919 (Folder 5.38)
  - Letter to Ethelyn from J. L. McKinney, 15 Apr 1919 (Folder 5.39)
  - Letter to Ethelyn from J. L. McKinney, 15 Apr 1919 (Folder 5.40)
  - Letter to Ethelyn from J. L. McKinney, 12 Aug 1919 (Folder 5.41)
  - Letter to Ethelyn from J. L. McKinney, 17 Aug 1919 (Folder 5.42)
  - Letter to unknown correspondent, signed M [Titusville, PA], 18 Aug [1919] (Folder 5.43)
  - Letter to Ethelyn and Lena from Aileen Ford McKinney, 19 Aug 1919 (Folder 5.44)
  - Letter to Ethelyn from J. L. McKinney, 19 Aug 1919 (Folder 5.45)
  - Letter to [Ethelyn?] from J. L. McKinney, [19 Aug 1919?] (Folder 5.46)
  - Letter to Ethelyn from J. L. McKinney with envelope, 21 Aug 1919 (Folder 5.47)
  - Letter to Ethelyn from (J. L. McKinney) [Clove Valley/La Grangeville, NY], 4 Apr 1920 (Folder 5.48)
  - Letter from (J. L. McKinney) to his granddaughter [Titusville, PA], 29 Oct 1920 (Folder 6.1)
  - Letter to Ethelyn from J. L. McKinney [La Grangeville, NY], 30 Dec 1920 (Folder 6.2)
  - Note to Ethelyn and photo of [J. L. McKinney?] at Martha's Vineyard, Sept 1921 (Folder 6.3)
  - Letter to Jean Webster McKinney from J. L. McKinney [Titusville, PA], 1 Mar 1923 (Folder 6.4)
  - Letter to Ethelyn from J. L. McKinney, 14 Mar 1923 (Folder 6.5)
  - Letter to Ethelyn from J. L. McKinney, 4 July 1924 (Folder 6.6)
  - Letter to Ethelyn from J. L. McKinney [Clove Valley, La Grangeville, NY], 11 Aug 1924 (Folder 6.7)
  - Letter to Ethelyn from J. L. McKinney [Hotel La Salle, New York], 17 Oct 1924 (Folder 6.8)
  - Letter to Ethelyn from J. L. McKinney [Hotel La Salle, New York], 19 Oct 1924 (Folder 6.9)
  - Letter to Ethelyn from J. L. McKinney [Hotel La Salle, New York], 26 Oct 1924 (Folder 6.10)
  - Letter to Ethelyn from J. L. McKinney [Titusville, PA], 28 Oct 1924 (Folder 6.11)
  - Letter to Ethelyn and Jean Webster McKinney from J. L. McKinney [Titusville, PA], 3 Nov 1924 (Folder 6.12)
  - Letter to Ethelyn from J. L. McKinney, 11 Nov 1924 (Folder 6.13)
  - Letter to Ethelyn and Jean Webster McKinney from J. L. McKinney [Titusville, PA], 25 Nov 1924 (Folder 6.14)
  - Letter to Ethelyn and Jean Webster McKinney from J. L. McKinney [Titusville, PA], 28 Nov 1924 (Folder 6.15)
  - Letter to Ethelyn from J. L. McKinney [Hotel La Salle, New York], 6 Dec 1924 (Folder 6.16)
  - Letter to Ethelyn from J. L. McKinney, 12 Dec 1924 (Folder 6.17)
  - Letter to Ethelyn from J. L. McKinney [Hotel La Salle, New York], 13 Jan 1925 (Folder 6.18)
  - Letter to Ethelyn from J. L. McKinney [New York, N.Y.], 11 Feb 1925 (Folder 6.19)
  - Letter to Ethelyn from J. L. McKinney, 19 Mar 1925 (Folder 6.20)
  - Letter to Ethelyn from J. L. McKinney [Hotel La Salle, New York], 21 Apr 1925 (Folder 6.21)
  - Letter to Ethelyn from Glenn [La Grangeville, NY], 23 May 1925 (Folder 6.22)
  - Letter to Ethelyn from J. L. McKinney [La Grangeville, NY], 24 May 1925 (Folder 6.23)
  - Letter to Ethelyn from Glenn [La Grangeville, NY], 27 May 1925 (Folder 6.24)
  - Letter to Ethelyn from J. L. McKinney [La Grangeville, NY], 30 May 1925 (Folder 6.25)
  - Letter to Ethelyn and Jean from J. L. McKinney [Hotel La Salle], 2 June 1925 (Folder 6.26)
  - Letter to Ethelyn from J. L. McKinney [Clove Valley, La Grangeville, NY], 11 June 1925 (Folder 6.27)
  - Letter to Ethelyn from J. L. McKinney [Hotel La Salle, New York], 16 June 1925 (Folder 6.28)
  - Letter to Ethelyn from J. L. McKinney, 19 June 1925 (Folder 6.29)
  - Letter to Ethelyn from J. L. McKinney, 21 June 1925 (Folder 6.30)
  - Letter to Ethelyn from J. L. McKinney, 29 June 1925 (Folder 6.31)
  - Letter to Ethelyn from J. L. McKinney [Titusville, PA], 5 July 1925 (Folder 6.32)
  - Letter to (Ethelyn and Jean) from J. L. McKinney, 11 July 1925 (Folder 6.33)
  - Letter to Ethelyn from J. L. McKinney, 17 July 1925 (Folder 6.34)
  - Letter to Ethelyn from J. L. McKinney, 22 July 1925 (Folder 6.35)
  - Letter to Ethelyn from J. L. McKinney, 28 July 1925 (Folder 6.36)
  - Letter to Ethelyn from J. L. McKinney, 5 Aug 1925 (Folder 6.37)
  - Letter to Ethelyn from J. L. McKinney [La Grangeville, NY], 21 Aug 1925 (Folder 6.38)
  - Letter to "Heart" (Ethelyn?) from J. L. McKinney [La Grangeville, NY], 22 Aug 1925 (Folder 6.39)
  - Letter to Ethelyn from J. L. McKinney [La Grangeville, NY], 11 Oct 1925 (Folder 6.40)
  - Letter to Ethelyn from J. L. McKinney [Hotel La Salle, New York], 22 Oct 1925 (Folder 6.41)
  - Letter to Ethelyn from J. L. McKinney, 1 Nov 1925 (Folder 6.42)
  - Letter to Ethelyn from J. L. McKinney [Titusville, PA], 14 Nov 1925 (Folder 6.43)
  - Letter to Ethelyn from J. L. McKinney [Hotel La Salle, New York], 3 Dec 1925 (Folder 6.44)
  - Letter to Ethelyn from J. L. McKinney [Hotel La Salle, New York], 5 Dec 1925 (Folder 6.45)
  - Letter to Ethelyn from J. L. McKinney [Titusville, PA], 15 Dec 1925 (Folder 6.46)
  - Letter to Ethelyn from J. L. McKinney [New York], 18 Dec 1925 (Folder 6.47)
  - Letter to Ethelyn from J. L. McKinney [New York], 31 Dec 1925 (Folder 6.48)
  - Biographical info for Jon Curtis McKinney and Clipping "J.C. McKinney Dead", undated (Folder 6.49)
  - Letter to Ethelyn from J. L. McKinney [Hotel La Salle, New York], 19 Feb 1926 (Folder 6.50)
  - Letter to Ethelyn from J. L. McKinney, 24 Mar 1926 (Folder 6.51)
  - Letter to Ethelyn from J. L. McKinney, 1 Apr 1926 (Folder 6.52)
  - Letter to Ethelyn from J. L. McKinney, 9 Apr 1926 (Folder 6.53)
  - Letter to Ethelyn from J. L. McKinney [Titusville, PA], 19 Apr 1926 (Folder 6.54)
  - Letter to Ethelyn from J. L. McKinney [La Grangeville, NY], 16 May 1926 (Folder 6.55)
  - Letter to Ethelyn from J. L. McKinney [Titusville, PA], 25 May 1926 (Folder 6.56)
  - Letter to Jean Webster McKinney from J. L. McKinney with envelope [New York], 27 June 1926 (Folder 6.57)
  - Letter to Ethelyn from J. L. McKinney [Titusville, PA], 1 July 1926 (Folder 6.58)
  - Letter to Ethelyn from J. L. McKinney, 5 July 1926 (Folder 6.59)
  - Letter to Ethelyn from J. L. McKinney, 6 July 1926 (Folder 6.60)
  - Letter to Ethelyn from J. L. McKinney [La Grangeville, NY], 29 Aug 1926 (Folder 6.61)
  - Letter to Ethelyn from J. L. McKinney [Hotel La Salle, New York], 15 Sept 1926 (Folder 6.62)
  - Letter to Ethelyn from J. L. McKinney [New York], 24 Sept 1926 (Folder 6.63)
  - Letter to Ethelyn from J. L. McKinney [La Grangeville, NY], 30 Sept 1926 (Folder 6.64)
  - Letter to Ethelyn from J. L. McKinney [Hotel La Salle, New York], 19 Oct 1926 (Folder 6.65)
  - Letter to Ethelyn from J. L. McKinney, 25 Oct 1926 (Folder 6.66)
  - Letter to Ethelyn from J. L. McKinney, 31 Oct 1926 (Folder 6.67)
  - Letter to Ethelyn from J. L. McKinney, 11 Nov 1926 (Folder 7.1)
  - Letter to Ethelyn from J. L. McKinney [Hotel La Salle, New York], 19 Nov 1926 (Folder 7.2)
  - Letter to Ethelyn from J. L. McKinney [La Grangeville, NY], 28 Nov 1926 (Folder 7.3)
  - Letter to Ethelyn from J. L. McKinney [Hotel La Salle, New York], 16 Jan 1927 (Folder 7.4)
  - Letter to Ethelyn from J. L. McKinney [Hotel La Salle, New York], 23 Jan 1927 (Folder 7.5)
  - Letter to Ethelyn from J. L. McKinney [New York], 26 Jan 1927 (Folder 7.6)
  - Letter to Ethelyn from J. L. McKinney [New York], 10 Feb 1927 (Folder 7.7)
  - Letter to Ethelyn from J. L. McKinney, 18 Feb 1927 (Folder 7.8)
  - Letter to Ethelyn from J. L. McKinney, 25 Feb 1927 (Folder 7.9)
  - Letter to Ethelyn from J. L. McKinney [Titusville, PA], 4 Mar 1927 (Folder 7.10)
  - Letter to Ethelyn from J. L. McKinney, 11 Mar 1927 (Folder 7.11)
  - Letter to Ethelyn from J. L. McKinney [Titusville, PA], 17 Mar 1927 (Folder 7.12)
  - Letter to Ethelyn from J. L. McKinney [Titusville, PA], 27 Mar 1927 (Folder 7.13)
  - Letter to Ethelyn from J. L. McKinney, 3 Apr 1927 (Folder 7.14)
  - Letter to Ethelyn from J. L. McKinney [La Grangeville, NY], 11 Apr 1927 (Folder 7.15)
  - Part of letter from J. L. McKinney [La Grangeville, NY], 12 May 1927 (Folder 7.16)
  - Letter to Ethelyn from J. L. McKinney [La Grangeville, NY], [16 May 1927?] (Folder 7.17)
  - Letter to Ethelyn from J. L. McKinney [New York], 20 June 1927 (Folder 7.18)
  - Letter to Ethelyn from J. L. McKinney, 24 June 1927 (Folder 7.19)
  - Letter to Ethelyn from J. L. McKinney, 8 July 1927 (Folder 7.20)
  - Letter to Ethelyn from J. L. McKinney [Titusville, PA], 19 July 1927 (Folder 7.21)
  - Letter to Ethelyn and Jean from J. L. McKinney Titusville, PA], 1 Nov 1927 (Folder 7.22)
  - Letter to (Ethelyn?) from J. L. McKinney [New York], 1927 (Folder 7.23)
  - Letter to Ethelyn from J. L. McKinney [La Grangeville, NY], 29 Nov 1927 (Folder 7.24)
  - Letter to Ethelyn from J. L. McKinney [New York], 27 Dec 1927 (Folder 7.25)
  - Letter to Ethelyn from J. L. McKinney, 9 Mar 1928 (Folder 7.26)
  - Letter to Ethelyn from J. L. McKinney [New York], 20 Mar 1928 (Folder 7.27)
  - Letter to Ethelyn from J. L. McKinney with envelope [La Grangeville, NY], 21 June 1928 (Folder 7.28)
  - Letter to Ethelyn from J. L. McKinney [Titusville, PA], 7 July 1928 (Folder 7.29)
  - Letter to Ethelyn from J. L. McKinney [La Grangeville, NY], 16 Sept 1928 (Folder 7.30)
  - Letter to Ethelyn from J. L. McKinney [Titusville, PA], 16 Sept 1929 (Folder 7.31)
  - Letter to Ethelyn from J. L. McKinney [Titusville, PA], 17 Sept 1929 (Folder 7.32)
  - Letter to Ethelyn from J. L. McKinney with envelope [La Grangeville, NY], 8 Oct 1928 (Folder 7.33)
  - Letter to Ethelyn from J. L. McKinney with envelope [New York], 25 Nov 1929 (Folder 7.34)
  - Letter to Ethelyn and Jean from J. L. McKinney [Southern Pines, NC], 1 Mar 1930 (Folder 7.35)
  - Letter to Ethelyn from J. L. McKinney [Southern Pines, NC], 4 Apr 1930 (Folder 7.36)
  - Letter to Ethelyn from J. L. McKinney [La Grangeville, NY], 22 June 1930 (Folder 7.37)
  - Letter to Ethelyn from J. L. McKinney [Titusville, PA], 22 July 1930 (Folder 7.38)
  - Letter to Ethelyn from J. L. McKinney [Titusville, PA], 21 Aug 1930 (Folder 7.39)
  - Letter to Ethelyn from J. L. McKinney [La Grangeville, NY], 25 Nov 1930 (Folder 7.40)
  - Letter to Ethelyn from J. L. McKinney with envelope [New York], 18 May 1931 (Folder 7.41)
  - Typewritten letter to Ethelyn and Jean from J. L. McKinney with envelope [Southern Pines, NC], 15 Apr 1932 (Folder 7.42)
  - Letter to J. L. McKinney from Clarence M. Wooley [New York], 20 June 1932 (Folder 7.43)
  - Letter to Ethelyn from J. L. McKinney with envelope [Southern Pines, NC], 2 Feb 1933 (Folder 7.44)
  - Letter to Ethelyn from J. L. McKinney with envelope [Southern Pines, NC], 7 Mar 1933 (Folder 7.45)
  - Titusville Herald Clipping re: J. L. McKinney's 91st Birthday/ and an envelope addressed to Ethelyn, 21 July 1933 (Folder 7.46)
  - Letter from J. L. McKinney to Glenn [Titusville, PA], 27 July 1933 (Folder 7.47)
  - Letter to Ethelyn from J. L. McKinney with envelope [Titusville, PA], 28 July 1933 (Folder 7.48)
  - Letter to Ethelyn from J. L. McKinney [New York], 2 Jan 1934 (Folder 7.49)
  - Letter to Ethelyn from J. L. McKinney [Southern Pines, NC], 25 Jan 1934 (Folder 7.50)
  - Letter to Ethelyn from J. L. McKinney [Southern Pines, NC], 29 Jan 1934 (Folder 7.51)
  - Letter to Ethelyn from J. L. McKinney [Southern Pines, NC], 5 Feb 1934 (Folder 7.52)
  - Letter to Ethelyn from J. L. McKinney [Southern Pines, NC], 9 Feb 1934 (Folder 7.53)
  - Letter to Ethelyn and Jean from J. L. McKinney [Southern Pines, NC], 19 Feb 1934 (Folder 7.54)
  - Letter to Ethelyn and Jean from J. L. McKinney [Southern Pines, NC], 1 Mar 1934 (Folder 7.55)
  - Letter to Ethelyn and Jean from J. L. McKinney with envelope [Southern Pines, NC], 12 Apr 1934 (Folder 7.56)
  - Letter to Ethelyn from J. L. McKinney [New York], 28 Apr 1934 (Folder 8.1)
  - Letter to Ethelyn and Jean from J. L. McKinney [La Grangeville, NY], 6 May 1934 (Folder 8.2)
  - Letter to Ethelyn from J. L. McKinney [New York], 18 May 1934 (Folder 8.3)
  - Letter to Ethelyn from J. L. McKinney [New York], 29 May 1934 (Folder 8.4)
  - Letter to Ethelyn from J. L. McKinney [Titusville, PA], 26 Jun 1934 (Folder 8.5)
  - Letter to Ethelyn from J. L. McKinney [Titusville, PA], 2 July 1934 (Folder 8.6)
  - Letter to Ethelyn from J. L. McKinney, 3 July 1934 (Folder 8.7)
  - Clippings re: J. L. McKinney's Death, 29 Sept 1942 (Folder 8.8)
  - Snapshot of Harriet McKinney Clawson at 82.5 years, 1920 (Folder 8.8)
  - Letter to Ann Clawson from Leo R. McKinney [Lakeland, FL.], 26 Nov 1940 (Folder 8.9)
  - New York Times Clipping re: J. L. McKinney's Obituary, 22 May 1937 (Folder 8.10)
  - New York Times Clipping re: J. L. McKinney's Obituary, 21 May 1937 (Folder 8.11)
  - New York Herald Tribune Clipping re: J. L. McKinney's Obituary, 22 May 1937 (Folder 8.12)
  - Associated Press Obituary of J. L. McKinney, 21 May 1937 (Folder 8.13)
  - J. L. McKinney's Obituary from the New York Tribune, 21 May 1937 (Folder 8.14)
  - J. L. McKinney's Obituary in The Daily Item [Port Chester, NY], 22 May 1937 (Folder 8.15)
  - J. L. McKinney's Obituary in the Titusville Record, 21 May 1937 (Folder 8.16)
  - Clipping in the Titusville Record, "John L. McKinney Dies Here, in his 95th Year", 21 May 1937 (Folder 8.17)
  - J. L. McKinney's Obituary in The Greenwich Press, 27 May 1937 (Folder 8.18)
  - J. L. McKinney's Obituary in the Daily News Graphic [Greenwich, Conn.], 22 May 1937 (Folder 8.19)
  - J. L. McKinney's Obituary in the New York American, 21 May 1937 (Folder 8.20)
  - Acknowledgement of Sympathy card from Mrs. J. L. McKinney, undated (Folder 8.21)
  - Letter to Ethelyn with envelope from The Press Association Compilers, Inc., 2 Feb 1937 (Folder 8.22)
  - Biography of J. L. McKinney by The Press Association Compilers, Inc., 1937 (Folder 8.23)
  - Portrait of J. L. McKinney with bill to The American Historical Society, Inc., Jan 1932 (Folder 8.24)
  - Clipping from the Daily News Graphic, re: pictures of John D. Rockefeller through various stages of his life, 24 May 1937 (Folder 8.25)
  - John D. Rockefeller's Obituary in the Daily News Graphic, 24 May 1937 (Folder 8.26)
  - Clipping from Greenwich Press, "Rockefeller Name Linked with Greenwich...", 27 May 1937 (Folder 8.27)
  - Clipping re: J. L. McKinney's political involvement and clipping re: funeral services for Aileen Ford McKinney, undated (Folder 8.28)
  - Clipping re: Remodeling of J. L. McKinney's barn into a modern dwelling, 2 Sept 1948 (Folder 8.29)
  - Official Program of the Diamond Jubilee of Oil, Titusville, PA, 24-27 Aug 1934 (Folder 8.30)
  - Invitation to the 75th Anniversary of the Discovery of Oil in the Drake Well, 1934 (Folder 8.31)
  - Letter to Ethelyn from James h. Caldwell re: gift to the Drake Well Memorial Park, 3 Jan 1941 (Folder 8.32)
  - Letter to Ethelyn from James h. Caldwell re: gift to the Drake Well Park Advisory Committee, 3 Jan 1941 (Folder 8.33)
  - Clippings re: Drake Well, 1934 (Folder 8.34)
  - Clippings re: Ethelyn McKinney's Gift to Drake Well Park, 1940 (Folder 8.35)
  - New York Times clipping, "First Well Ready to Sprout Again", 27 Aug 1949 (Folder 8.36)
  - Clipping re: Technicolor movie of Edwin C. Drake, 27 Feb 1955 (Folder 8.37)
  - NY Times Book Review of The Great Oilorado, 22 Feb 1959 (Folder 8.38)
- SERIES IV. John C. Ford
  - Obituary of John C. Ford in the Titusville Morning Weekly, 18 Sept 1896 (Folder 9.1)
  - Letter to Ethelyn from Glenn Ford McKinney, [1896?] (Folder 9.2)
  - Photographs, undated (Folder 9.3)
    1 photograph of John C. Ford and 1 photograph of his grave
  - Photocopy of pp.12-13 in Revolutionary Soldiers of Warren County, Pennsylvania re: James and Lieut. Robert Arthur, undated (Folder 9.4)
- SERIES V. Jerusha Jane Dalrymple Ford
  - Letter to Susan Jane McKinney from Jerusha, 19 Mar 1841 (Folder 9.5)
  - Letter to Susan Jane McKinney from Jerusha, [Mar 1841?] (Folder 9.6)
  - Letter to Susan Jane McKinney from Jerusha, 1841 (Folder 9.7)
  - Letter to Ethel from "Grand-Ma" (Jerusha aka Grandma Ford) [Pittsfield, PA], 12 Aug 1841 (Folder 9.8)
  - Letter to Glenn Ford McKinney from Grandma Ford with envelope [Pittsfield PA], 14 Feb 1889 (Folder 9.9)
  - Letter to Mrs. J. L. McKinney (Ida Ford McKinney) from Jerusha [Pittsfield, PA], 12 Feb 1890 (Folder 9.10)
  - Photo of J. L. McKinney, Ethelyn, and Grandma Ford at the Oregon Coast, 1895 (Folder 9.11)
  - Letter to Ethelyn from Grandma Ford with envelope [Titusville, PA], 3 May [1897?] (Folder 9.12)
  - Letter to Ethelyn from Grandma Ford [Titusville, PA], 11 May 1907 (Folder 9.13)
  - Letter to Ethelyn from Grandma Ford with envelope, 14 Mar [1908] (Folder 9.14)
  - Jerusha Jane Dalrymple Ford's Obituary, 30 Oct 1909 (Folder 9.15)
  - Letter to Ethelyn from Avery H. Stone with envelope [Minneapolis, Minn.], 7 Jan 1910 (Folder 9.16)
  - Clipping re: history of Dalrymple family and 2 notes on genealogy, undated (Folder 9.17)
  - Notes re: Dalrymple Ford lineage, undated (Folder 9.18)
  - Notes re: Dalrymple-Washburne Lineage, undated (Folder 9.19)
  - Photograph of Grandmother Ford, undated (Folder 9.20)
- SERIES VI. Ida DeEtte Ford McKinney
  - Ida Ford's Journal including account of the trip from Brokenstraw Creek to Louisville, KY, 28 Mar-4 May 1865 (Folder 9.21)
  - "The Wreath" and poetry, undated (Folder 9.22)
  - Letter to John McKinney from Ida Ford with envelope, 26 July 1863 (Folder 9.23)
  - Letter to J. L. McKinney from Ida Ford, 4 Aug 1863 (Folder 9.24)
  - Letter to J. L. McKinney from Ida Ford [Pittsburgh, PA], 8 Sept 1863 (Folder 9.25)
  - Letter to J. L. McKinney from Ida with envelope, 20 Sept 1863 (Folder 9.26)
  - Letter to J. L. McKinney from Ida with envelope, 25 Oct 1863 (Folder 9.27)
  - Letter to J. L. McKinney from Ida, 27 Dec 1863 (Folder 9.28)
  - Letter to Ida from Vincent Ford (her uncle) with envelope [Martinsburgh, W. Va.], 7 Jan 1864 (Folder 9.29)
  - Letter to J. L. McKinney from Ida with envelope, 15 Jan 1864 (Folder 9.30)
  - Letter to J. L. McKinney from Ida, 24 Feb 1864 (Folder 9.31)
  - Letter to J. L. McKinney from Ida with envelope, 24 Apr, 1864 (Folder 9.32)
  - Letter to J. L. McKinney from Ida with envelope, undated (Folder 9.33)
  - Letter to J. L. McKinney from Ida with envelope [Pittsfield, PA], 17 July 1864 (Folder 9.34)
  - Letter to J. L. McKinney from Ida with envelope [Pittsfield, PA], 31 July 1864 (Folder 9.35)
  - Letter to J. L. McKinney from Ida [Pittsfield, PA], 28 Aug1864 (Folder 9.36)
  - Letter to J. L. McKinney from Ida with envelope, 18 Sept1864 (Folder 9.37)
  - Letter to J. L. McKinney from Ida with envelope [Pittsfield, PA], 20 Nov 1864 (Folder 9.38)
  - Letter to J. L. McKinney from Ida with envelope [Pittsfield, PA], 1 Jan 1865 (Folder 9.39)
  - Letter to J. L. McKinney from Ida with envelope [Pittsfield, PA], 12 Feb 1865 (Folder 9.40)
  - Letter to J. L. McKinney from Ida with envelope [Pittsfield, PA], 18 June 1865 (Folder 9.41)
  - Letter to J. L. McKinney from Ida with envelope [Pittsfield, PA], 27 Aug 1865 (Folder 9.42)
  - Letter to J. L. McKinney from Ida with envelope [Pittsfield, PA], 3 Sept 1865 (Folder 9.43)
  - Letter to J. L. McKinney from Ida with envelope [Pittsfield, PA], 14 Sept 1865 (Folder 9.44)
  - Letter to J. L. McKinney from Ida with envelope [Pittsfield, PA], 14 Nov 1865 (Folder 9.45)
  - Letter to J. L. McKinney from Ida with envelope [Pittsfield, PA], 10 Dec 1865 (Folder 9.46)
  - Letter to J. L. McKinney from Ida with envelope [Pittsfield, PA], 20 Dec 1865 (Folder 9.47)
  - Letter to J. L. McKinney from Ida with envelope, [23 Dec 1865?] (Folder 9.48)
  - Letter to J. L. McKinney from Ida with envelope, 4 Jan 1866 (Folder 10.1)
  - Description of "My Photograph Album" by Ida Ford, 4 Jan 1866 (Folder 10.2)
  - Letter to J. L. McKinney from Ida with envelope, 14 Jan 1866 (Folder 10.3)
  - Letter to J. L. McKinney from Ida with envelope, 21 Jan 1866 (Folder 10.4)
  - Letter to J. L. McKinney from Ida with envelope, 30 Jan 1866 (Folder 10.5)
  - Letter to J. L. McKinney from Ida with envelope, 9 Feb 1866 (Folder 10.6)
  - Letter to J. L. McKinney from Ida, [11 Feb 1866?] (Folder 10.7)
  - Letter to J. L. McKinney from Ida, 20 Feb 1866 (Folder 10.8)
  - Letter to J. L. McKinney from Ida, 29 Feb 1866 (Folder 10.9)
  - Letter to J. L. McKinney from Ida with envelope [Pittsfield, PA], 18 Mar 1866 (Folder 10.10)
  - Letter to J. L. McKinney from Ida with envelope [Pittsfield, PA], 23 Mar 1866 (Folder 10.11)
  - Letter to J. L. McKinney from Ida with envelope, 4 Apr 1866 (Folder 10.12)
  - Letter to J. L. McKinney from Ida with envelope [Pittsfield, PA], 15 Apr 1866 (Folder 10.13)
  - Letter to J. L. McKinney from Ida with envelope [Pittsfield, PA], 22 Apr 1866 (Folder 10.14)
  - Letter to J. L. McKinney from Ida with envelope [Pittsfield, PA], 29 Apr 1866 (Folder 10.15)
  - Letter to J. L. McKinney from Ida with envelope, 17 May 1866 (Folder 10.16)
  - Letter to J. L. McKinney from Ida with envelope, undated (Folder 10.17)
  - Business card for McKinney Oil Company, undated (Folder 10.18)
  - Concert program for Public Exercises at the Genesee Lyceum, 30 May 1866 (Folder 10.18)
  - Concert Ticket, undated (Folder 10.18)
  - Letter to J. L. McKinney from Ida, 4 June 1866 (Folder 10.19)
  - Letter to J. L. McKinney from Ida with envelope [Pittsfield, PA], 12 June1866 (Folder 10.20)
  - Letter to J. L. McKinney from Ida with envelope [Pittsfield, PA], 20 June 1866 (Folder 10.21)
  - Letter to J. L. McKinney from Ida with envelope [Pittsfield, PA], 26 June 1866 (Folder 10.22)
  - Faded letter to J. L. McKinney from Ida with envelope, 24 Oct 1866 (Folder 10.23)
  - Letter to J. L. McKinney from Ida with envelope [Pittsfield, PA], 8 Nov 1866 (Folder 10.24)
  - Faded letter to J. L. McKinney from Ida with envelope [Pittsfield, PA], 16 Dec 1866 (Folder 10.25)
  - Faded letter to J. L. McKinney from Ida with envelope, 27 Dec 1866 (Folder 10.26)
  - Faded letter to J. L. McKinney from Ida with envelope [Pittsfield, PA], 30 Dec 1866 (Folder 10.27)
  - Letter to J. L. McKinney from Ida with envelope [Pittsfield, PA], 1867 (Folder 10.28)
  - Letter to J. L. McKinney from Ida with envelope, 1867 (Folder 10.29)
  - Marriage Certificate for J. L. McKinney and Ida Ford, 24 Feb 1867 (Folder 10.30)
  - Photo of Ida Ford, 1863 (Folder 10.31)
  - Letter to J. L. McKinney from Ida with envelope, 17 Apr 1867 (Folder 10.32)
  - Letter to "Father and Mother" from Ida Ford with envelope, 6 Oct 1864 (Folder 10.33)
  - Letter to J. L. McKinney from Ida with envelope [Pittsfield, PA], 3 Nov 1864 (Folder 10.34)
  - Letter to J. L. McKinney from Ida with envelope, 6 Nov 1867 (Folder 10.35)
  - Letter to (Ida?) from Jean McMaster, [18 Feb 1869?] (Folder 10.36)